let savollar7 = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "to abandon",
      answer: "C. tashlab ketmoq",
      options: [
        "A. saqlamoq",
        "B. qaytmoq",
        "C. tashlab ketmoq",
        "D. ko'chmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "ambitious",
      answer: "A. maqsadli",
      options: [
        "A. maqsadli",
        "B. dangasa",
        "C. kamtar",
        "D. befarq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "to bark",
      answer: "D. hurmoq",
      options: [
        "A. miyovlamoq",
        "B. bo'kirmoq",
        "C. sayramoq",
        "D. hurmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "bay",
      answer: "B. ko'rfaz",
      options: [
        "A. sohil",
        "B. ko'rfaz",
        "C. daryo",
        "D. ko'l"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "brilliant",
      answer: "C. ajoyib",
      options: [
        "A. ahmoq",
        "B. oddiy",
        "C. ajoyib",
        "D. o'rtacha"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "chin",
      answer: "A. iyak",
      options: [
        "A. iyak",
        "B. peshona",
        "C. yonoq",
        "D. burun"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "complaint",
      answer: "D. shikoyat",
      options: [
        "A. maqtov",
        "B. taklif",
        "C. iltimos",
        "D. shikoyat"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "deaf",
      answer: "B. kar",
      options: [
        "A. ko'r",
        "B. kar",
        "C. soqov",
        "D. cho'loq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "enthusiastic",
      answer: "C. zavqlangan",
      options: [
        "A. zerikarli",
        "B. xafa",
        "C. zavqlangan",
        "D. befarq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "expedition",
      answer: "A. ekspeditsiya",
      options: [
        "A. ekspeditsiya",
        "B. sayohat",
        "C. sayr",
        "D. safar"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 11,
      question: "horizon",
      answer: "D. ufq",
      options: [
        "A. osmon",
        "B. quyosh",
        "C. bulut",
        "D. ufq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 12,
      question: "loyal",
      answer: "B. sodiq",
      options: [
        "A. xoin",
        "B. sodiq",
        "C. dushman",
        "D. befarq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 13,
      question: "mayor",
      answer: "C. hokim",
      options: [
        "A. vazir",
        "B. prezident",
        "C. hokim",
        "D. sudya"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 14,
      question: "mutual",
      answer: "A. o'zaro",
      options: [
        "A. o'zaro",
        "B. bir tomonlama",
        "C. turli",
        "D. shaxsiy"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 15,
      question: "overweight",
      answer: "D. juda semiz",
      options: [
        "A. ozg'in",
        "B. nozik",
        "C. kelishgan",
        "D. juda semiz"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 16,
      question: "refuge",
      answer: "B. boshpana",
      options: [
        "A. xavf",
        "B. boshpana",
        "C. yashirinish",
        "D. uy"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 17,
      question: "to restore",
      answer: "C. tiklamoq",
      options: [
        "A. buzmoq",
        "B. yangilamoq",
        "C. tiklamoq",
        "D. ta'mirlamoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 18,
      question: "to rub",
      answer: "A. ishqalamoq",
      options: [
        "A. ishqalamoq",
        "B. urmoq",
        "C. bosmoq",
        "D. qashimoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 19,
      question: "senses",
      answer: "B. sezgi organlari",
      options: [
        "A. his-tuyg'ular",
        "B. sezgi organlari",
        "C. fikrlar",
        "D. nervlar"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 20,
      question: "veterinarian",
      answer: "C. veterinar",
      options: [
        "A. shifokor",
        "B. tish doktor",
        "C. veterinar",
        "D. hamshira"
      ]
    }
  ];
  
export default savollar7;